Pancho的舒适科学工程，这就是我们的项目是
Pancho's comfort sciences engineering and that's our project is the father of
and that's our project is the father of I scale it allows realization
我缩放它可以实现
这个内容和巴比伦怎么办
and that's our project is the father of I scale it allows realization
what with this content and Babylon
我们的氧气在物理上并置
our oxygens are collocated physically
他们很高兴
and they were happy
主要是我们在2014年去了发送者和参议院
it's mostly we go to the sender and Senate in 2014
we go to the sender and Senate in 2014 and we go stock unit director for my
因为我有许多不同的救恩方式，所以我去了股票部门主管
and we go stock unit director for my because many different still salvation
because many different still salvation so only one feel alive today and so
所以今天只有一个人还活着，所以没有国家或实施
so only one feel alive today and so there is no countries or implementation
there is no countries or implementation in 2014 but a remarkable achievements
在2014年，但在国际
in 2014 but a remarkable achievements can be provided in international
can be provided in international measures where there are enormous
工业界和工业界付出巨大努力的措施
measures where there are enormous efforts both from industry and
efforts both from industry and they invested to this field so a lot of
他们在这个领域投入了很多知识，否则你会回答
they invested to this field so a lot of learnings and else you're gonna answer
learnings and else you're gonna answer on experience
靠经验哦，真的
on experience oh really
oh really so my whole thing to follow him he'll
所以我跟随他的整个事情他都会明白
so my whole thing to follow him he'll understand
和
with
[音乐]
[Music]
他们也程序
they also procedure
居民激励
the resident incentive
冒险实际上一直在试图使一些
adventures it's actually been trying to make some
it's actually been trying to make some sort of internship
实习
只是表情符号句子可以在此块中描述，并且这些停顿之间
it's actually been trying to make some sort of internship
just emoticon sentences can be described in this block and these pauses between
只是表情符号句子可以在此块中描述，并且这些停顿之间
in this block and these pauses between world
世界
[音乐]
in this block and these pauses between world
[Music]
[音乐]
和
[Music]
and
两个大比目鱼的儿子，但你只知道他们想
the son of two halibut you only knew they wanted to
哦
Oh
这里有一个很高的单一配方
there's a high single formula up here
[音乐]
[Music]
功能丧失
lost function
最后
and finally
[音乐]
[Music]
和
and
有一些场合
there are some occasions
[音乐]
[Music]
在今天的前五名中，我们太复杂了，模型太简单了，我们
in today's top five we were too complicated model simple very hot and we
complicated model simple very hot and we can
能够
[音乐]
complicated model simple very hot and we can
[Music]
直觉等于还是很简单
the intuitive is equal to is still simple
太多了
too much
否或
no or
并使用我的形式
and using the form of my
[音乐]
[Music]
一个显然
one apparently
和
and
[音乐]他们想忽略
[Music] they'll want to ignore
they'll want to ignore oh please for geography
哦，请查询地理哦
oh please for geography Oh
电永远不会穿他们，因为他们喜欢来
electric never wear em because they like to come by
如果您要编辑我的尺寸
if you'll edit my size
事实上电影《幻想曲》中的野牛
in fact a buffalo in film Fantasia extra
所以所有那些
so with all those
和四种不同的颜色
and four different color
但如果不仅有像比尔这样的人告诉梦想中的家，
but if there's no only feel like a people like Bill told the dream home
people like Bill told the dream home life's real castle
生活的真实城堡
他的生活可能很美，也许对其他客人来说
people like Bill told the dream home life's real castle
his life can be beautiful maybe for other guests
与其他常识互动很令人兴奋
it's been exciting to interact with other common sense
一切
everything
你们都平常吗
are you all common
因为当帐单在那儿的时候
because when the bill was right there
整个阶段都吃华夫饼的自然色
and eat natural color of waffle work all over the stage that
over the stage that [Music]
[音乐]不同于大多数
[Music] unlike most all of it
unlike most all of it [Music]
[音乐]哦
[Music] Oh
与海洋对齐
with ocean alignment
你好
hi
哦
Oh
在我的面前，这是一个疯狂的科学家或老师，毫无疑问地讲了这么多话
in my face this is a crazy scientist or teacher telling without question so much
teacher telling without question so much all those tickets are a year of conquer
所有这些门票都是征服欧洲的一年。
all those tickets are a year of conquer Europe this fortune different features
Europe this fortune different features and opportunity of all penalties amazing
和所有惩罚的机会，惊人的生物
and opportunity of all penalties amazing creatures
creatures all the clothing falling in touch with
所有的衣服都与艾米和
all the clothing falling in touch with both Amy and
那些孩子在那里有25,000个牙科学院
and those kids are along on 25,000 college of dentistry there
college of dentistry there that's slightly on faceted and the very
略微切面，并且此框提供的人员非常多
that's slightly on faceted and the very people that are provided by this box
people that are provided by this box it's also a binary package equivalent
这也是一个二进制程序包等效测试，仅像哦100个样本和
it's also a binary package equivalent test only like Oh 100 samples and the
test only like Oh 100 samples and the relative truth of 1810 was 14
1810年的相对真相是14
以及反对的立场和619的附带常数
test only like Oh 100 samples and the relative truth of 1810 was 14
and the yeah stance against it and the incidental constants of 619
以及反对的立场和619的附带常数
and the incidental constants of 619 position we completed the first one you
位置我们完成了第一个你有我的罪过
position we completed the first one you have my sin
哦
Oh
超过人
over people
却无法满足图片尺寸和
without fulfilling to image size and
我们将配件与迭代器保持在一起，并且
we kept our accessories with the iterator and
iterator and it's the most function value and this is
这是最实用的价值，这只是一种宗教，
it's the most function value and this is only one religion and
所以积累和旋转
and
so the accumulation and spinning and
与所有的黄金
with all the gold
[音乐]
[Music]
这里
here
还有这个苹果
and this Apple
[音乐]
[Music]
我们有有趣的残疾令人恶心
we have fun disabilities that's disgusting
例如
for example
[音乐]
[Music]
我们爱
we love
通过您的基本思想对我的知识的看法
the opinion of my knowledge through your basic thinking
是的
yeah
没看到
didn't see
我们可以看到我的孩子度过的时光
we can see the times of my children go through
1:44哦
1:44 Oh
Oh to
至
如果你喜欢他们正在调查他们的家人，那是因为
Oh to
and if you like a little like you're investigating their family huh because
如果你喜欢他们正在调查他们的家人，那是因为
investigating their family huh because every
每一个
是的，感觉就像
investigating their family huh because every
and yeah feels like
[音乐]
[Music]
听这些更多的阐述
listen to these more elaboration
考虑到工作地点范围内的选拔代理人标准
think about choice agent standard within the assignment over the freaking place
确切地说，我们了解更多[音乐]
exactly we learn more [Music]
解决方案更小
the solution is smaller and
是确切的问题
is the exact problem
[音乐]很多艺术家
[Music] a lot of artists
美丽或
beautiful or
哦
Oh
几乎
almost
[掌声]
[Applause]
哦，是的，我想我很喜欢，因为你曾经
Oh agency yeah I suppose me feel fancy because you're ever
because you're ever the beginning stage of commotion on a
领导者抵制的真正的通勤的开始阶段
the beginning stage of commotion on a real I resisted by the leaders for
real I resisted by the leaders for passive occasions like some conflicts
像一些冲突这样的消极场合今天相互吸引了我的图像网格
passive occasions like some conflicts attracted each other today my image mesh
attracted each other today my image mesh also attracted by
也被吸引
在我的旅行分类示例中，通常有很多南美
attracted each other today my image mesh also attracted by
in my example to classify a trip there are typically a lot of South America
在我的旅行分类示例中，通常有很多南美
are typically a lot of South America have different features of action and
有不同的动作特征和谈论是否倾向
have different features of action and the tendencies to talk about whether
the tendencies to talk about whether this is good or not
这是好还是不好
好的，大家好，我说我是尼克·日内瓦（Nick Geneva），我想介绍一下
the tendencies to talk about whether this is good or not
all right hello everyone says I'm Nick Geneva and I want to presenting on
好的，大家好，我说我是尼克·日内瓦（Nick Geneva），我想介绍一下
Geneva and I want to presenting on comprising graphical models with my
用我的原始标题组成的图形模型是神经网络，但是
comprising graphical models with my original title was neural networks but
original title was neural networks but we're going to generalize it to machine
我们将其推广到机器学习中以进行结构化表示
we're going to generalize it to machine learning for structural representation
好的，所以本来我想这个演讲是一个故事
all right so originally this I guess this presentation is kind of a story of
this presentation is kind of a story of how I was originally going to focus on
我本来打算如何在2016年这里重点关注这篇论文的
how I was originally going to focus on this paper up here this 2016 there's
this paper up here this 2016 there's paper then basically got lost in one of
基本上，这些论文实际上就被其中的一篇参考文献所迷惑了。
paper then basically got lost in one of the references which actually ended up
the references which actually ended up proposing that did I found kind of
提议我发现了一种有趣且难以理解的东西
proposing that did I found kind of interesting and hard to understand
interesting and hard to understand because it motivated a lot of what kind
因为它激发了很多正在发生的想法
because it motivated a lot of what kind of ideas that are happening up in this
of ideas that are happening up in this one so yeah all right starting off when
是的，是的，当我们建立模型时，可以开始
one so yeah all right starting off when we're building a model where the model
we're building a model where the model to represent data a model to generate
表示数据的模型通常会生成您想要的任何一天
to represent data a model to generate day of whatever you want generally you
day of whatever you want generally you may have two different goals you may
可能有两个不同的目标，您可能需要一个灵活的方法，所以
may have two different goals you may want to have a flexible approach so
want to have a flexible approach so let's say you have some non parametric
假设您有一些复杂的高的非参数表示
let's say you have some non parametric representation of some complex high
representation of some complex high dimensional data or you may want to
维数据，或者您可能希望构建我们的方法，这可能是
dimensional data or you may want to structure our approach and this may be
structure our approach and this may be to find a structure representation of
查找可以概括的数据的结构表示形式
to find a structure representation of data that can then be generalized
data that can then be generalized perhaps so in terms of platform model
也许就平台模型而言，这就是我所说的灵活模型时的意思。
perhaps so in terms of platform model that's when I say flexible models I mean
that's when I say flexible models I mean like I said I'm talking about these
就像我说的我在谈论这些黑匣子方法，所以机器学习
like I said I'm talking about these black box methods so machine learning
black box methods so machine learning you're looking for buzzword like neural
您正在寻找像神经网络卷积网络这样的流行词
you're looking for buzzword like neural networks convolutional Network
networks convolutional Network autoencoders Gans support vector
自动编码器Gans支持向量机aa网站结构模型
autoencoders Gans support vector machines aa website structure model
machines aa website structure model course PGM class so it's all about
当然是PGM课程，所以这全都与概率图形模型有关
course PGM class so it's all about probabilistic graphical models stuff
probabilistic graphical models stuff where we actually have values that means
在这里，我们实际拥有的价值意味着某些东西，而不仅仅是随机的
where we actually have values that means something rather than just random
something rather than just random weights and stuff that they're just kind
权重和东西，它们只是某种功能的匹配，所以这个问题
weights and stuff that they're just kind matching up a function so the question
matching up a function so the question is what do we want what happens if we
我们想要的是什么如果我们既想要A的灵活性又想要
is what do we want what happens if we want both A's flexible yet also
want both A's flexible yet also structured approach so this means
结构化的方法，所以这实际上意味着，如果我想让我们
structured approach so this means essentially like if I want like let's
essentially like if I want like let's say like I have some high dimensional
就像我有一些需要映射的高维数据一样
say like I have some high dimensional data that I need to map or something
data that I need to map or something with some flexible method but I also
用一些灵活的方法，但是我还想要一些值，然后
with some flexible method but I also want some sort of values I can then
want some sort of values I can then relate to maybe physical dynamics
与物理动力有关，实际舞会有些事
relate to maybe physical dynamics there's something about the actual prom
there's something about the actual prom because of that price so just the
因为这个价格，所以问题只是作为一种激励
because of that price so just the problem to kind of motivate this as an
problem to kind of motivate this as an example so let's suppose that we have
这个例子，让我们假设我们在这座山的内部
example so let's suppose that we have this mountain that's inside of this
this mountain that's inside of this spherical container moving around and
球形容器移动，我们的输入数据将是一些
spherical container moving around and our input data is going to be some
our input data is going to be some height so basically our input is this
高度，所以基本上我们的输入就是这张图片，而当我们输出时
height so basically our input is this image and from that when our output
image and from that when our output debase be the interest in trouble
降低对本质上鼠标的故障结构的兴趣
debase be the interest in trouble structure of essentially the mouse's
structure of essentially the mouse's actual behavior so these may be the
实际行为，因此可能是当前的舞蹈编辑或动作
actual behavior so these may be the current of dance edits in or movement no
current of dance edits in or movement no I'm not so as they clearly have this
我不是这样，因为他们清楚地收到了这个高维图像，所以我们
I'm not so as they clearly have this high dimensional image coming in so we
high dimensional image coming in so we kind of want a flexible model to learn
我想要一个灵活的模型来学习，但是我们想要的输出
kind of want a flexible model to learn that but then our output we want to have
that but then our output we want to have some sort of probabilistic inference on
关于鼠标动作可能的某种概率推断
some sort of probabilistic inference on what's probably of the mouse's actions
what's probably of the mouse's actions sitting up on its hind legs or if it's
坐在它的后腿上，或者如果它在挠耳和类似的东西
sitting up on its hind legs or if it's scratching its ear and stuff like that
scratching its ear and stuff like that those are very structured output on so
这些都是非常结构化的输出，因此基本上是一种组合，
those are very structured output on so basically one kind of a combination and
basically one kind of a combination and that's kind of a whole main idea of this
这是本文的主要主题，也是我觉得越来越冷的一种感觉
that's kind of a whole main idea of this paper and kind of cold I think growing
paper and kind of cold I think growing field is essentially can we combine
我们基本上可以将这些领域结合起来以构建更强大的建模工具
field is essentially can we combine these to build stronger modeling tools
these to build stronger modeling tools that can really get the best of both
真正可以兼得两全其美的本质是它，为此，我们
that can really get the best of both worlds is essentially it so for this we
worlds is essentially it so for this we won't be looking at might we be looking
不会看，也许我们会看一些更沉闷的东西
won't be looking at might we be looking at something a little bit more dull
at something a little bit more dull which is a natural clustering frog so
这是一个自然的聚集青蛙，所以这只是一个例子，这是一个真正的
which is a natural clustering frog so these are just an example it's a really
these are just an example it's a really great toy problem on one we'll be
我们将要看到的一个巨大的玩具问题是螺旋形的问题，也许在
great toy problem on one we'll be looking at is spiral problems maybe in a
looking at is spiral problems maybe in a spiral and the reason for that is one
螺旋上升，原因之一是它们都在两个以内，这很棒
spiral and the reason for that is one it's great they're both within two
it's great they're both within two also it's these clusters are very
这些集群都是我们想要的非常离散的集群
also it's these clusters are very discrete clusters that we want to you
discrete clusters that we want to you know categorize though each one of these
知道分类，尽管您想找到的每个分类都是不同的
know categorize though each one of these you want to just find is a different
you want to just find is a different class however they are still there
上课，但是他们仍然是非大学的，所以在那里
class however they are still there non-college so there and this is
non-college so there and this is unsupervised learning problem so they
无监督的学习问题，所以他们睡觉你没有任何标签，所以
unsupervised learning problem so they sleep you don't have any labels so
sleep you don't have any labels so before we get into the actual paper room
在进入实际的纸室之前，请访问我们的老朋友高斯混合物
before we get into the actual paper room visit our old friend Gaussian mixture
visit our old friend Gaussian mixture models to go over so this is the
模型，所以这是非贝叶斯公式，我发现了这一点，
models to go over so this is the non-bayesian formulation I find this and
non-bayesian formulation I find this and Bishop just to review if you're like me
主教只是想回顾一下您是否像我一样，并怀念我们倾向于的金鱼
Bishop just to review if you're like me and have a memory of a goldfish we tend
and have a memory of a goldfish we tend to forget this stuff however the idea of
忘记这些东西，但是生态混合模型的想法是，我们有一个
to forget this stuff however the idea of Ecology mixture model is that we have a
Ecology mixture model is that we have a latent variable Z which is binary
潜在变量Z是二进制变量，表示哪个类别的
latent variable Z which is binary variable which represents which class of
variable which represents which class of which cause mixture we're pulling from
导致我们从中混合的原因，对于每种原因，我们都要确保
which cause mixture we're pulling from and we have for each causing make sure
and we have for each causing make sure we have respective mean and it also
我们有各自的平均值，也有精度，我们可以增加复杂度a
we have respective mean and it also precision we can increase complexity a
precision we can increase complexity a little bit and make it kind of more
并通过引入一些使它变得更多的贝叶斯相关性
little bit and make it kind of more Bayesian correlation by introducing some
Bayesian correlation by introducing some priors onto our precision and all
先验我们的精确度和所有确定性，这不是
priors onto our precision and all certainty which is T nope here these are
certainty which is T nope here these are our high performers that we're
我们要介绍的高绩效人才，所以这仅仅是一些
our high performers that we're introducing so this is just some
introducing so this is just some reminders again if you want to know more
再次提醒您，如果您想了解更多评分，请刷新您的记忆
reminders again if you want to know more much rating so just refresh your memory
much rating so just refresh your memory so again our joint distribution it's
再次，我们的联合分布将是
so again our joint distribution it's going to be a the multiplication of
going to be a the multiplication of essentially like including our priors or
本质上就像包括我们的先验一样，可能性采取以下形式：
essentially like including our priors or not the likelihood takes the form of
not the likelihood takes the form of course our cause in C is binary
当然，我们在C中的原因是二进制的
是的，只是混合系数，我们会通过它快速完成-我
not the likelihood takes the form of course our cause in C is binary
yeah just mixing coefficients we're just gonna go kind of fast through this - I
是的，只是混合系数，我们会通过它快速完成-我
gonna go kind of fast through this - I have greens on afterwards
后来果岭开了，但这里只用了什么东西，所以
have greens on afterwards yet only used a anything here alright so
yet only used a anything here alright so just to refresh your memory for actually
只是为了刷新您的记忆，以便进行此问题的调整
just to refresh your memory for actually on conducting for tuning this problem
on conducting for tuning this problem are legit
在法国是合法的，今天是什么样子
are legit in France and whatnot it's day like
in France and whatnot it's day like someone to enum algorithms with this
有人用这个贝叶斯算法来枚举他们尚未接受的算法
someone to enum algorithms with this Bayesian that they've yet to take kind
Bayesian that they've yet to take kind of a variational approach which involves
涉及使下界最大化的变分方法，我们都知道
of a variational approach which involves maximizing lower bound we all know that
maximizing lower bound we all know that and it's an alternative estimate we came
这是另一种估计，我们来回之间是必要的
and it's an alternative estimate we came Kong back and forth between essential
Kong back and forth between essential updating responsibilities computing the
更新职责，计算与那些相关的统计数据
updating responsibilities computing the relevant statistics related to those
relevant statistics related to those responsibilities and also updating the
责任并更新您必须跳过的超参数空间
responsibilities and also updating the hyper parameters space you have to jump
hyper parameters space you have to jump back and forth between these two then
在这两者之间来回交流，然后将实际解收敛于
back and forth between these two then converge the actual solution in
converge the actual solution in particular mission we don't know now the
我们现在不知道的特定任务这个感兴趣的问题是
particular mission we don't know now the problem with this problem of interest is
problem with this problem of interest is basically we can't actually describe
基本上，我们实际上不能非常有效地描述这些区域，就像
basically we can't actually describe these regions very efficiently and like
these regions very efficiently and like a hint said that before we chose us prom
提示说，在我们选择舞会之前，特别是因为这些确实是
a hint said that before we chose us prom specifically because these are indeed
specifically because these are indeed there they don't really fit college so
他们根本不适合大学，所以即使我们能够
there they don't really fit college so essentially even though we're able to
essentially even though we're able to fit the data through mixture we don't
通过混合拟合数据，我们实际上并没有得到五个离散类
fit the data through mixture we don't really get the five discrete classes
really get the five discrete classes that we actually originally wanted so
我们原本想要的，所以让我们完整地看一看
that we actually originally wanted so let's look at something completely
let's look at something completely different now let's say all right so
现在不一样了，我们说这是结构化的结果，所以现在
different now let's say all right so this was the structured result so now
this was the structured result so now let's go to entirely flexible is all an
让我们去完全灵活，这里的所有想法就是现在而不是
let's go to entirely flexible is all an idea here is that now instead of
idea here is that now instead of essentially having you know this mixture
从本质上讲，您知道这种混合监护人将基本上是
essentially having you know this mixture guardians were going to basically be
guardians were going to basically be using a narrow network since you predict
使用狭窄的网络，因为您可以预测均值和过程
using a narrow network since you predict to predict a mean and also a procedure
所以现在这是我们的可能性，您会看到我们的实际均值以及
so this is now our likelihood and you see that our our actual mean and also
see that our our actual mean and also our precision is now so wait biases of
我们的精度现在是神经网络的等待偏差，现在这实际上是
our precision is now so wait biases of the neural network now this is actually
the neural network now this is actually a function that's basically being
现在基本上在这里产生的功能当然是问题
a function that's basically being produced here now of course the issue
produced here now of course the issue with this is obvious
很明显，我们已经失去了所有的分类
with this is obvious we've lost all the sort of categorizing
we've lost all the sort of categorizing is essentially it sure we can fit this
从本质上讲，我们可以很好地适应这一点，从而获得非常好的密度
is essentially it sure we can fit this very nicely we get very nice densities
very nicely we get very nice densities where the actual data is but in the way
实际数据在哪里，但以对不同实际数据进行分类的方式
where the actual data is but in the way of classifying the different actual
of classifying the different actual clusters Bravo
聚集Bravo好吧，现在关于要发表的论文
clusters Bravo alright so now about which papers to
alright so now about which papers to this later paper back in 2012 and I'm
这是2012年的这篇论文，我在谈论一种方法，
this later paper back in 2012 and I'm talking about a method which is kind of
talking about a method which is kind of general approach car rat the mixture
通用方法大鼠混合模型和核心思想本质上是
general approach car rat the mixture models and the core idea is essentially
models and the core idea is essentially in its name so we're going to take a
以它的名字命名，所以我们将采用混合模型，在左侧
in its name so we're going to take a mixture model so on the left and
mixture model so on the left and basically wrap it and some sort of
基本上包装它和某种功能，基本上可以转换
basically wrap it and some sort of function that transforms basically the
function that transforms basically the the latent variable was returned
将针对混合模型确定的潜在变量返回到
the latent variable was returned determined for the mixture model into a
determined for the mixture model into a non Gaussian and spacing on garden
非高斯和间隔动物的本质，所以这个想法是
non Gaussian and spacing on garden animals essentially so the idea is that
animals essentially so the idea is that instead of using them as the direct
而不是将它们用作通过某种方式映射它的直接输出
instead of using them as the direct output along map it through some sort of
output along map it through some sort of function do they get a much more complex
函数是否可以获得更复杂的输出，但仍将保留
function do they get a much more complex output yet will also retain the
output yet will also retain the structured representation
结构化表示
所以这就是我们在这里要看的东西，所以基本上所有东西都有
output yet will also retain the structured representation
so here's what we're looking at on here so basically everything most of it has
所以这就是我们在这里要看的东西，所以基本上所有东西都有
so basically everything most of it has remained the same I'll talk about this
保持不变，我将继续讨论并分解更多细节，但前提是
remained the same I'll talk about this and break down more detail but only if
and break down more detail but only if now at this arbitrary function over here
现在在这里的任意功能上，为此，我们将要
now at this arbitrary function over here and for this and the paper we're gonna
and for this and the paper we're gonna be following it it's gonna be a Gaussian
跟随它，这将是一个高斯过程，所以里根在左边
be following it it's gonna be a Gaussian process so Reagan is down on the left
process so Reagan is down on the left this is actually precisely the Bayesian
这实际上正是我们拥有的高斯混合模型上的贝叶斯模型
this is actually precisely the Bayesian on Gaussian mixture model that we had
on Gaussian mixture model that we had before
之前，实际上除了钥匙
before exactly actually except the key
exactly actually except the key difference is that now the outputs are
区别在于，现在的输出不是实际的观测值，不是
difference is that now the outputs are not the actual observations they're not
not the actual observations they're not a set of latent variables so these don't
一组潜在变量，因此它们实际上并没有真正的含义
a set of latent variables so these don't actually have really true meaning
actually have really true meaning they're not what we're seeing isn't it's
他们不是我们所看到的，不是我们也想要的实际数据
they're not what we're seeing isn't it's not what our actual data I also want to
not what our actual data I also want to note here that I personally I predefined
请注意，我个人预定义了一组混合成分k
note here that I personally I predefined a set of mixture components k however
a set of mixture components k however you can indeed have a infinite set which
您确实可以有一个无限的集合，这就是他们在论文中通过
you can indeed have a infinite set which is what they do in the paper through a
is what they do in the paper through a Derrick wave process and give sampling
井架波过程并提供采样
Derrick wave process and give sampling of that
现在在右边基本上这将是我们的高斯过程
now on the right side basically this is now going to be our Gaussian process
now going to be our Gaussian process here so basically it's going to be
在这里，基本上将这些潜在变量映射到一个
here so basically it's going to be mapping these latent variables here to a
mapping these latent variables here to a non ecology manifold is the idea and I
非生态流形是这个主意，我留在这里，这是一个高斯
non ecology manifold is the idea and I stay here that this is a Gaussian
stay here that this is a Gaussian process however on this is not actually
流程，但实际上并不包含在内，因此您可以将此想法扩展到
process however on this is not actually inclusive so you can extend this idea to
inclusive so you can extend this idea to others or a methods however you want
其他或方法，但是您实际上想要一个想要的地图
others or a methods however you want actually one of the map how you wanted
actually one of the map how you wanted to find this function um it's just what
找到这个功能，这就是我们启动的功能，我们正在做这个特殊的
to find this function um it's just what we launched we're doing this particular
we launched we're doing this particular paper um I do know here that they're
嗯，我在这里确实知道他们基本上是这样，所以我们在这里
paper um I do know here that they're basically so this right here we have
basically so this right here we have inputs our latent variables on that the
输入我们的潜在变量，以毫米为单位，这恰好是
inputs our latent variables on that the in mm process and this is precisely a
in mm process and this is precisely a Gaussian process lake imperative model
如果我们忽略此封闭部分，则实际上是高斯过程湖势在必行模型
Gaussian process lake imperative model in fact if we ignore this closed section
in fact if we ignore this closed section out here and we just take these guys as
在这里，我们只是把这些家伙当成基本固定的，这实在是一个艰巨的任务
out here and we just take these guys as basically fixed it's precisely a gauntly
basically fixed it's precisely a gauntly so in essence you can view this as a
因此，从本质上讲，您可以将其视为GPL的通用版本，因此，如果
so in essence you can view this as a more generalized version of GPL so if
more generalized version of GPL so if you like me and you're not too well
你喜欢我，首先在薄纱和潜伏变量方面不太好
you like me and you're not too well first on gauzy and upon latent variable
first on gauzy and upon latent variable models we're gonna go over it so the
我们将要讨论的模型，所以这个想法的关键原则是
models we're gonna go over it so the idea the the key principle is that
idea the the key principle is that instead of having circle represent your
而不是让圆圈通过德国高斯表示您的可能性，并且
instead of having circle represent your likelihood through a German Gaussian and
likelihood through a German Gaussian and your actual covariance matrix is going
您实际的协方差矩阵将通过内核函数定义
your actual covariance matrix is going to be defined through a kernel function
to be defined through a kernel function down here now the key thing that makes
现在在这里，使创新成为典范的关键是
down here now the key thing that makes this innovation very models is that this
this innovation very models is that this kernel function is governed through
内核函数是通过潜在变量控制的，因此这些变量是
kernel function is governed through latent variables so these variables are
latent variables so these variables are related to your actually do get related
与您的实际关系确实相关，但是存在主要变量
related to your actually do get related but there's been leading variables
but there's been leading variables basically it now of course we need to
基本上现在，我们当然需要优化这些潜在变量，所以我们
basically it now of course we need to optimize these latent variables so we
optimize these latent variables so we needed to tune this model so you can get
需要调整此模型，以便您基本上可以完成此操作，从而获得所需的结果
needed to tune this model so you can get desired result on that is done basically
desired result on that is done basically if ingredient based operations
如果基于成分的操作优化是的，那么我很快
if ingredient based operations optimization and yeah so I just quickly
optimization and yeah so I just quickly list some gradients here you can see
在这里列出一些渐变，您可以看到基本上我们需要一个成本函数
list some gradients here you can see that basically we want a cost function
that basically we want a cost function or you know what I like over here like a
或者你知道我喜欢这里的东西，就像观察笔记
or you know what I like over here like a note of observation is getting laid
note of observation is getting laid variables and also the data is gonna
变量以及数据将代表我们的参数以及GPM和
variables and also the data is gonna represent our parameters and the GPM and
represent our parameters and the GPM and essentially this using chain rule you
基本上，这是使用链式规则，您可以看到，基本上，
essentially this using chain rule you can see that basically this combined
can see that basically this combined with this will give you the derivative
这样做会给您成本函数的导数，因此您的
with this will give you the derivative of the of your cost function so your
of the of your cost function so your wall of your likelihood with respect to
关于您的实际潜在变量的可能性墙被消耗了
wall of your likelihood with respect to your actual latent variable be consumed
好了，现在进入实际文件，以便我们将其分解
alright so now moving into the actual paper now so we're gonna break this down
paper now so we're gonna break this down and look into three parts of this actual
并研究一下我想谈论的说唱混合模型的这一实际部分
and look into three parts of this actual of this rap mixture model I want to talk
of this rap mixture model I want to talk about a generation this is a generative
关于一代，这是一个生成模型，我不谈论训练
about a generation this is a generative model I don't talk about the training of
model I don't talk about the training of it they don't talk about on briefly
他们没有在简短的预测中谈论它，所以它是热能ppl
it they don't talk about on briefly prediction so it's thermal energy ppl
prediction so it's thermal energy ppl Fiona song
菲奥娜（Fiona）歌曲本质上这是一个生成模型
Fiona song essentially this is a generative model
essentially this is a generative model so we can generate realizations from
因此我们可以从此PGM基本生成器生成实现，而不是
so we can generate realizations from this PGM basic generator instead of
this PGM basic generator instead of latent variables and feed it through our
潜在变量，并通过我们的高斯过程将其馈送到非高斯
latent variables and feed it through our Gaussian process on to non Gaussian
Gaussian process on to non Gaussian manifolds idea so the idea is I surmise
流形的想法，所以我想这是三个步骤，尽管每个步骤
manifolds idea so the idea is I surmise it's in three steps though for each
it's in three steps though for each component for volume to I remember going
我记得在这里回到我们的PGM，所以第一步
component for volume to I remember going back to our PGM here so the first step
back to our PGM here so the first step is that we want to draw precision and it
是我们要绘制精度，这也意味着从
is that we want to draw precision and it also mean for each component right from
also mean for each component right from our priors who's here
我们的先驱们总是在这里，尽管我们总是在定义
our priors who's here somewhere as we always define though
somewhere as we always define though there's a Wishart distribution and the
这里有一个Wishart分布以及这里的社会病理学和分布
there's a Wishart distribution and the social pathology and distribution here
social pathology and distribution here we can then draw a function so this is
然后我们可以绘制一个函数，所以这基本上是如果您先于
we can then draw a function so this is basically if you have priors over your
basically if you have priors over your actual parameters and you're calling
实际的参数，你打电话给我，我应该画那些
actual parameters and you're calling processed me I should draw those
processed me I should draw those parameters for your GP and that foreign
您的GP和那位外籍女士的参数很长
parameters for your GP and that foreign lady here function that's a long map
lady here function that's a long map user space and for for each desired
用户空间，然后针对每个所需的观察，您就可以
user space and for for each desired observation that you want you can then
observation that you want you can then draw a assignment so you just choose
绘制作业，所以您只需选择想要的班级，然后从该绘制中
draw a assignment so you just choose which class you want and from that draw
which class you want and from that draw a set of latent variables from your T
一组来自您的T GM的潜在变量，这是由它们的原因引起的，而您
a set of latent variables from your T GM's this is from their cause in and you
GM's this is from their cause in and you seek those X's through your dogs and
通过狗和可能的发电机寻找那些X
seek those X's through your dogs and possible generator why
possible generator why now that's nice but we still have to
现在很好，但是我们仍然要担心我们如何实际得到这个
now that's nice but we still have to worry about how do we actually get this
worry about how do we actually get this model to mark how do we trade it so we
模型来标记我们如何进行交易，因此我们拥有两个系统，它们比
model to mark how do we trade it so we have two systems on or over further than
have two systems on or over further than two systems in this you have the PGM and
在这两个系统中，您拥有PGM和GP，我们将成为
two systems in this you have the PGM and also the GP and we're going to be
also the GP and we're going to be optimizing those simultaneously and
同时优化这些，基本上要最大化
optimizing those simultaneously and basically what you want to maximize are
basically what you want to maximize are displayed here like there's a billion
在这里显示，就像有十亿个变量，所以这是不同的
displayed here like there's a billion variables so this is different
variables so this is different originally than our GP procedure but
最初比我们的GP程序要好，但是如果我们扩展它，我们会看到
originally than our GP procedure but however if we expand it out we see that
however if we expand it out we see that actually his and this is a kind of core
实际上是他的，这是一种核心思想，从本质上讲，我们拥有
actually his and this is a kind of core idea here is that essentially we have we
idea here is that essentially we have we break it apart yes you have a loop
分解它是的，您有一个来自我们高斯的电循环
break it apart yes you have a loop electrically that was from our Gaussian
electrically that was from our Gaussian process but then we have essentially
流程，但从本质上讲，您可以将其视为先验的
process but then we have essentially this you can consider it like a prior is
this you can consider it like a prior is basically it so we have this complex
基本上是这样，所以我们有一个复杂的先验被标记到我们的
basically it so we have this complex prior that's getting tagged on to our
prior that's getting tagged on to our loss function which is then going to
损失函数，然后将要改善其性能，这是
loss function which is then going to improve its performance and this is
improve its performance and this is basically this idea right here is the
基本上，这里的想法与实际使用的想法相同
basically this idea right here is the same concept that is used actually also
same concept that is used actually also in the 2000 sticking paper that I was
在我本应该真正专注于2000年的粘纸上，但这是
in the 2000 sticking paper that I was supposed to really focus on but it's the
supposed to really focus on but it's the same with the same idea essentially
相同的想法本质上是他们致力于更复杂的
same with the same idea essentially they're tacking on a more complex more
they're tacking on a more complex more descriptive prior on to their loss
在描述其损失函数之前
descriptive prior on to their loss function
function which basically allows them to do a lot
基本上可以让他们做很多事
which basically allows them to do a lot who were stuff
是的，因此可以在此基础上进行改进
yes so to kind of evolve this on in this
so to kind of evolve this on in this paper they use a hybrid Monte Carlo or
论文他们使用混合蒙特卡洛或哈密尔顿蒙特卡洛辩论
paper they use a hybrid Monte Carlo or Hamiltonian Monte Carlo debate please
Hamiltonian Monte Carlo debate please sample I say kind of move because I need
样本我之所以说这样一种举动，是因为我需要来自背景方面
sample I say kind of move because I need coming from a background in terms of
coming from a background in terms of research I think gradient but it's
研究，我认为是梯度，但它是采样，所以一个采样一组
research I think gradient but it's sampling so one sample a set of
sampling so one sample a set of particles from basically this posterior
基本上来自这个后部的粒子，所以这个想法本质上是
particles from basically this posterior here so the idea there is essentially
here so the idea there is essentially we're going to have an additional set of
如果您还记得HMC，我们将有另外一组潜在变量
we're going to have an additional set of latent variables if you recall HMC
latent variables if you recall HMC basically we're then going to propagate
基本上，我们接下来将使用哈密顿动力学来传播它们，以便
basically we're then going to propagate those using hamiltonian dynamics so to
those using hamiltonian dynamics so to do that you meet the gradient the
你是否满足梯度，这里的梯度实际上就是
do that you meet the gradient the gradient here is actually so if we take
gradient here is actually so if we take the log of the rights the logs put it
日志所赋予的权利的日志，那么您就拥有了这些的总和
the log of the rights the logs put it across then you have this sum of these
across then you have this sum of these so we call that the gradient here is
所以我们称这里的梯度恰好来自我们的GP，这就是
so we call that the gradient here is exactly comes from our GP so that's we
exactly comes from our GP so that's we already have these here and then the
在这里已经有这些了，然后我们的先验的导数是解析的
already have these here and then the derivative of our prior is analytical
derivative of our prior is analytical because it's a PGM and we can control we
因为它是一个PGM，我们可以控制，所以我们可以说
because it's a PGM and we can control we can say that
can say that nice distributions here that allows us
这里不错的分布，让我们您知道这吸引人
nice distributions here that allows us you know find this attractable
you know find this attractable actual long solution
实际的长期解决方案
所以是的，一旦用HMC采样了粒子，就以B为基数，所以
you know find this attractable actual long solution
so yeah so base B once once the particles are sampled with HMC so
所以是的，一旦用HMC采样了粒子，就以B为基数，所以
particles are sampled with HMC so essentially we have a set then propagate
本质上我们有一个集合，然后通过他的集合量传播一点到
essentially we have a set then propagate a little bit through his set amounts to
a little bit through his set amounts to that so like 25 or whatever we then
大概是25或其他，然后我们更新PCM，基本上就是这个新集合
that so like 25 or whatever we then update the PCM so basically this new set
update the PCM so basically this new set of particles within which are latent
内有潜在变量的粒子的观测值
of particles within which are latent variables act as observations for the
variables act as observations for the PGM and in a sense she then we take over
PGM，从某种意义上说，她然后我们接管了，我们将
PGM and in a sense she then we take over and we do the standard mixture of
and we do the standard mixture of garbage in optimization process you know
在优化过程中出现垃圾，您知道变式方法，或者
garbage in optimization process you know the variational approach or if you're
the variational approach or if you're not so in the Bayesian and DM approach
在最佳峰的贝叶斯和DM方法中不是这样，然后
not so in the Bayesian and DM approach at an optimized peak and then you go
at an optimized peak and then you go back you return to the document process
返回到您优化的文档流程，基本上重复一次
back you return to the document process you optimize and basically on you repeat
you optimize and basically on you repeat you jump back and forth so in summary
您来回跳动，因此总的来说，基本上我们有一套培训
you jump back and forth so in summary essentially we have a set of training
essentially we have a set of training observations Y we have an initial set of
观察Y我们有一个初始的潜在变量集被打包
observations Y we have an initial set of latent variable is packed however
latent variable is packed however looking for each training parameters
在这里寻找每个训练参数，所以theta再次是我们的高斯
looking for each training parameters here so theta again is our Gaussian
here so theta again is our Gaussian process parameters so length scales or
工艺参数，长度范围或其他一些噪声项，以及
process parameters so length scales or whatever some additional noise terms and
whatever some additional noise terms and then these are all part of our actual
那么这些都是我们实际PDF的一部分，因此第一步是
then these are all part of our actual PDF so the first step is that we're
PDF so the first step is that we're going to calculate the gradient of our
要计算我们的潜力的梯度，那么我们的行为很少
going to calculate the gradient of our potential here we're then little conduct
potential here we're then little conduct agency so essentially we're going to
代理机构，因此从本质上讲，我们将采用每一个微粒，否则我将搬家
agency so essentially we're going to take every single particle or I'll move
take every single particle or I'll move it a little bit a little bit a little
往后方一点点，然后那个
it a little bit a little bit a little bit toward the posterior and then that
bit toward the posterior and then that sample right there after stead amount of
经过固定的步骤之后，就可以在那里进行采样，然后将其作为一组新的
sample right there after stead amount of steps will then act as a new set of
steps will then act as a new set of waiting observations for the
从这里等待概率图形模型的观察
waiting observations for the probabilistic graphical models from here
probabilistic graphical models from here we then conduct the inference on the PGM
然后，我们在迭代之间的PGM上进行推断
we then conduct the inference on the PGM we iterate back and forth between
we iterate back and forth between computing the responsibilities and
计算职责和实际参数超参数
computing the responsibilities and actual parameters the hyper parameters
actual parameters the hyper parameters and we update them and then down here I
我们对其进行了更新，然后在这里我没有提及，但实际上
and we update them and then down here I did not mention this but essentially the
did not mention this but essentially the the parameters and the Guardian process
参数和监护程序也通过代理进行更新，因此
the parameters and the Guardian process are also updated through agency also so
are also updated through agency also so basically they sample length scales and
基本上他们会采样长度尺度和噪声项，然后慢慢传播
basically they sample length scales and noise terms and slowly propagate those
noise terms and slowly propagate those as well and basically this entire
以及基本上整个过程，然后一遍又一遍地循环
as well and basically this entire process and then it looped over and over
process and then it looped over and over and over until you team convergent or
直到您的团队趋同或达到您的时代
and over until you team convergent or your epoch has been reached
your epoch has been reached alright yes this is a quick on
好的，这是关于预测的快速讨论
alright yes this is a quick on discussion regarding the predictive
discussion regarding the predictive distribution so this is a little bit
分配，所以这有点涉及本质上
distribution so this is a little bit it's a little bit involved essentially
it's a little bit involved essentially we have to do a Monte Carlo
不幸的是，我们必须最后进行一次蒙特卡洛近似
we have to do a Monte Carlo approximation unfortunately last and
approximation unfortunately last and unfortunately but yeah and the main
不幸的是，是的，其背后的主要原因是因为我们
unfortunately but yeah and the main reason behind that is because we're
reason behind that is because we're using monstro it's actually sampled
使用monstro，实际上可以轻松地对变量进行采样并对其进行优化，但是
using monstro it's actually sampled easily in variables and optimize it but
easily in variables and optimize it but I will say here that on so breaking
我在这里要说的是，如此分散实际的预测分布
I will say here that on so breaking apart actual predictive distribution
apart actual predictive distribution where Y stars weren't guaranteed
不能保证对Y星感兴趣的观测和
where Y stars weren't guaranteed observation that were interested in and
observation that were interested in and X star is going to be so if we kind of
X星将是这样，如果我们将其拆分并分离，我们可以看到
X star is going to be so if we kind of split this up and separate it we can see
split this up and separate it we can see that this guy here this is actually done
这个家伙实际上是通过代理完成的，所以这是完成了三个
that this guy here this is actually done through agency so this is it done three
through agency so this is it done three agencies this is also so this is
代理商也是这样，这基本上是通过抽样完成的
agencies this is also so this is basically done by sampling we
basically done by sampling we marginalized yeah so we compute this by
是边缘化的，所以我们本质上是通过玩一堆新游戏来计算
marginalized yeah so we compute this by essentially and playing a bunch of new
essentially and playing a bunch of new flaking variables from our PGM and
从我们的PGM中提取变量并通过网络将其转发给
flaking variables from our PGM and feeding them forward through the network
feeding them forward through the network and this right here is actually the GP
这实际上是GP预测分布
and this right here is actually the GP predictive distribution which there's
predictive distribution which there's actually playing analytical for because
实际上是出于分析目的，因为这只是离奇
actually playing analytical for because it's just bizarre
好的
all right
还在生气，我不知道是哪个
still angry work I don't know which
我没有网路
I have no internet
好吧，反正我会在这里说明一下
okay all right well anyway I'll just I'll just kind of illustrate this here
I'll just kind of illustrate this here so essentially this if you look on the
所以基本上，如果你看幻灯片，这基本上是一部电影
so essentially this if you look on the slides basically this is a movie that
slides basically this is a movie that illustrates this whole process so the
说明了整个过程，所以想法是，在右侧，我们有一个
illustrates this whole process so the idea is that on on the right we have a
idea is that on on the right we have a set of observations and a spiral
一组观察结果和一个螺旋线，基本上这些都是我们通过GP得出的
set of observations and a spiral basically these we through the GP on
basically these we through the GP on these are translated to variables that
这些被转换为变量，然后我们通过HMC PGM传播这些变量
these are translated to variables that we then propagate through HMC the PGM
we then propagate through HMC the PGM then tries to map instead of mixtures
然后尝试在其上映射而不是混合，然后在此处，然后
then tries to map instead of mixtures onto that and then over here we then
onto that and then over here we then basically sample a bunch from these and
基本上从这些中取样一堆，然后通过
basically sample a bunch from these and then this represents the standpoint by
then this represents the standpoint by the colors and there's also shows in the
颜色，并且在纸上还显示了如何
the colors and there's also shows in the paper of how
还有我们的早餐有任何问题
and also our breakfast any question
[掌声]
[Applause]
大家下午好，我会谈论最近的论文
good afternoon everyone I'll be talking about the paper that has been recently
about the paper that has been recently published in 2017 that is a learning in
于2017年发布，该书旨在学习异构数据的网络结构
published in 2017 that is a learning in network structure of heterogeneous data
network structure of heterogeneous data by your pairwise exponential macro
通过您的成对指数宏随机字段，在此我们可以观察到
by your pairwise exponential macro random field and in this we can observe
random field and in this we can observe there are three main important keywords
有三个主要的重要关键词之一是学习网络
there are three main important keywords one is the learning the network
one is the learning the network structure second one is a word data
结构第二个是单词数据，它本质上是异构的，
structure second one is a word data it's a heterogeneous in nature and the
it's a heterogeneous in nature and the third one is what model we are going to
第三个是我们要与指数马尔可夫配对的模型
third one is what model we are going to want to pair with exponential Markov
want to pair with exponential Markov random field and this is the outline of
随机字段，这是我这件事的概述，我的意思是先跟我谈谈
random field and this is the outline of my this thing I mean talk to me first
my this thing I mean talk to me first I'll be giving an introduction of water
接下来，我将介绍水测试，但其动机是
I'll be giving an introduction of water test next but the motivation of its of
test next but the motivation of its of the work and then later the column
工作，然后是列定义，然后我会讲非常
the work and then later the column definition and then I'll be talking very
definition and then I'll be talking very in detail about pmrs and later since
有关pmrs的详细信息，以后再讲，因为有一个术语是分区
in detail about pmrs and later since there is one term that is the partition
there is one term that is the partition function which is not tractable so
函数是难处理的，因此在计算上我们去
function which is not tractable so computationally so we go for
computationally so we go for approximated or maximum like here
近似或最大值，例如此处，而不是精确的最大值
approximated or maximum like here instead of going for exact maximum
instead of going for exact maximum likelihood and then later I'll be
可能性，然后稍后我将讨论优化技术
likelihood and then later I'll be discussing about optimization technique
discussing about optimization technique called or a DMM that is alternating
被称为或DMM的交替方向或功率复用的方法
called or a DMM that is alternating direction or method of power multiplex
direction or method of power multiplex and then I will show a bleep result of
然后我将显示获得的结果的失败结果，然后得出结论
and then I will show a bleep result of what is obtained and then the conclusion
what is obtained and then the conclusion so what does and Markov random feel like
所以，马尔可夫随机觉得宏随机场的重要性是
so what does and Markov random feel like its importance of macro random field is
its importance of macro random field is like its importance is fundamental tool
就像它的重要性是机器学习中许多应用程序的基本工具
like its importance is fundamental tool to many applications in machine learning
to many applications in machine learning and also it is necessary for the samara
并且所有这些都需要轮回的异质性
and also it is necessary for the samara from all this a matter for heterogeneous
from all this a matter for heterogeneous entities so if for example you have a
实体，例如，如果您有一个医疗数据库和性质，那么这就是
entities so if for example you have a medical database and nature so that is
medical database and nature so that is it has between the categorical and
它介于类别变量和连续变量之间，因此例如
it has between the categorical and continuous variables so for example the
continuous variables so for example the age gender the medical history of the
年龄性别患者的病史和其他有趣的领域
age gender the medical history of the patient and the other interesting area
patient and the other interesting area where it can be used for analyzing the
可用于分析蛋白质相互作用的地方
where it can be used for analyzing the protein interaction
有一个主要的主要领域可以实现这一目标，那就是
there is one major major field which implements this and that is in
implements this and that is in computational biology which is the being
计算生物学这是无能为力的
computational biology which is the being unable to task for this is to
unable to task for this is to infrastructure and what is happening we
基础设施以及正在发生的事情
infrastructure and what is happening we now people and people who sees the
now people and people who sees the Gaussian graphical models but in
高斯图形模型，但在今天有了这种新技术
Gaussian graphical models but in nowadays with new technologies of this
nowadays with new technologies of this DNA sequencing we can which produces the
我们可以通过DNA测序来激活带有或不带有氮的数据
DNA sequencing we can which produces the data with or with nitrogen is activation
data with or with nitrogen is activation and this growth gaussian graphical
而且这种增长的高斯图形模型将无法提取
and this growth gaussian graphical models will not be able to extract
models will not be able to extract generate the structure for this
产生这个异质结构域的结构，因此
generate the structure for this heterogenous domain so because of this
heterogenous domain so because of this we are going to outline the entire now
我们现在将在运动问题中概述整个问题
we are going to outline the entire now in the sport questions we are going to
in the sport questions we are going to see what there's a PMRF and then second
看看有一个PMRF，然后我们将近似
see what there's a PMRF and then second we are going to of approximate the
we are going to of approximate the [Applause]
[鼓掌]公式最大近似值
[Applause] formula to approximate in maximum
formula to approximate in maximum likelihood problem and then develop
可能性问题，然后开发Avant，然后再进行分区功能
likelihood problem and then develop Avant and then on the partition function
Avant and then on the partition function in the later a scalable or a DML
在后来的封闭式可扩展或DML优化算法中
in the later a scalable or a DML optimization algorithm with the closed
optimization algorithm with the closed form update and then you'll also know
表格更新，然后您还将知道，如果我们的估计量是浮士德式的
form update and then you'll also know that if then our estimator is a Faustian
that if then our estimator is a Faustian so what is PMS going to diffuse of EMR
那么PMS将如何传播EMR，所以我们有一些定义
so what is PMS going to diffuse of EMR so there are some definitions that we
so there are some definitions that we are going to consider first we'll
首先要考虑的是，我们将数据视为
are going to consider first we'll consider that data is like an
consider that data is like an independent multiband observation and
独立的多频带观测，然后这些样本从
independent multiband observation and then later these samples are iid from an
then later these samples are iid from an exponential family of institution it's P
指数家族的机构是P的X逗号theta，然后是
exponential family of institution it's P of X comma theta and then later with
of X comma theta and then later with represented by P no graphical model with
用没有自然参数theta和的P无图形模型表示
represented by P no graphical model with the natural parameter theta and and we
the natural parameter theta and and we use these samples to estimate the
使用这些样本来估算下标分布，这是
use these samples to estimate the underling distribution and this is the
underling distribution and this is the in general like we have London PGM where
总的来说，就像我们有伦敦PGM，其中V是我的Nora顶点，E是我的优势
in general like we have London PGM where V is my Nora vertices and E is my edge
V is my Nora vertices and E is my edge and the length of this is P and also the
它的长度是P，并且结构也以此编码
and the length of this is P and also the structure is encoded with this
structure is encoded with this exponential family parameter theta so
指数族参数theta，因此PMRF pms是多元变量的子类
exponential family parameter theta so PMRF pms is a subclass of multivariate
PMRF pms is a subclass of multivariate exponent
可以解释的指数或指数族
or exponential family that can explain explicitly relieve the marker structure
显式缓解跨异构变量的标记结构，这里
explicitly relieve the marker structure across heterogeneous variables and here
across heterogeneous variables and here this these are the few notations that we
这些是我们将在这片轻落的片子中遵循的几个符号
this these are the few notations that we will follow in this light falling slice
will follow in this light falling slice the inner product is given by this
内积是由B的预告片给出的，还有明显的upma
the inner product is given by this trailer of a B and also the obvious upma
trailer of a B and also the obvious upma contaminate the set of very effectors in
以这种形式污染非常效应器集，所以让我们考虑
contaminate the set of very effectors in this form okay so let's consider a
this form okay so let's consider a random vector with X X 1 to X B and then
XX 1到XB的随机向量，然后是复古属且在
random vector with X X 1 to X B and then later which are retro genus and within
later which are retro genus and within this domain or extras a chronicle
这个域或多余的只是变量的编年史产品，那是什么
this domain or extras a chronicle product of just variables so what is it
product of just variables so what is it if you have a matrix a which is a 1 a 2
如果您有一个矩阵a，它是1 a 2 a 3 a 4和B，那么我们将每个矩阵相乘
if you have a matrix a which is a 1 a 2 a 3 a 4 and B so we multiply each
a 3 a 4 and B so we multiply each element of this a1 through this matrix B
这个a1的元素通过这个矩阵B和这个PHP来实现，这就是
element of this a1 through this matrix B and a to this PHP so that's the
and a to this PHP so that's the chronicle product here and then later or
在这里记述产品，然后再或假设我们有条件地分配
chronicle product here and then later or suppose we the conditional distribution
suppose we the conditional distribution of each variable is X are given all my
每个变量的X是给定我所有以前的PP减去1的变量
of each variable is X are given all my previous PP minus 1 variables are
previous PP minus 1 variables are unknown to be the exponential
未知的是该域中的指数分布是sy
unknown to be the exponential distribution in this domain is the sy
distribution in this domain is the sy are Thea ok so yeah and then later the
是Thea好的，是的，然后在此之后也指定了分布
are Thea ok so yeah and then later the distribution is also specified with this
distribution is also specified with this M R dimensional or potential with BR and
将BR和s BR转换为X Appa的MR尺寸或潜力，并基于我的比例
M R dimensional or potential with BR and s BR into X Appa and my scale based
s BR into X Appa and my scale based parameters TR into extra part and then
参数TR变成多余的部分，然后我让K这就是这种方式
parameters TR into extra part and then my let the K this is the way this is the
my let the K this is the way this is the main Joint Distribution for this the
此条件的主要联合分配条件是我的X对XP等于1
main Joint Distribution for this the condition is that my X is 1 to XP you
condition is that my X is 1 to XP you should follow this joint distribution
应该遵循这个联合分布，其中theta是我的分区
should follow this joint distribution where a of theta is my partition
where a of theta is my partition function and theta is my the no
函数和theta是我的no参数，抱歉此X参数和
function and theta is my the no parameter sorry this X parameter and the
parameter sorry this X parameter and the sweetest monitor is my parameter so yeah
最甜蜜的监视器是我的参数，所以从theta 1到theta P，所以我们的马尔代塔是
sweetest monitor is my parameter so yeah theta 1 to theta P so we're maldita is
theta 1 to theta P so we're maldita is the node parameter and the big theta is
node参数和大theta是我的订单Kappa theta是我的H参数
the node parameter and the big theta is my order Kappa theta is my H parameter
my order Kappa theta is my H parameter and your Peter make a lock partition
和你的彼得做一个锁分区功能，这表达在
and your Peter make a lock partition function which is expressed in this
function which is expressed in this equation ok
等式好了，现在这是一个简短的摘要，例如
equation ok so now this is a small brief like like
so now this is a small brief like like we're going to say we're going to define
我们要说的是要根据这个指数定义X的P
we're going to say we're going to define this P of X in terms of this exponential
this P of X in terms of this exponential family expression so where B of X is
家庭表达，所以X的B就是足够的统计量
family expression so where B of X is nothing but when sufficient statistic
nothing but when sufficient statistic this is my base parameter and a of theta
这是我的基本参数，theta的a是我的分区函数，这个内部
this is my base parameter and a of theta is my partition function and this inner
is my partition function and this inner product I define it in this fashion okay
我以这种方式定义产品好吗
所以下一个重要的事情是在一个节点上发生了什么
is my partition function and this inner product I define it in this fashion okay
so the next important thing is what happens at one node so one a conditional
所以下一个重要的事情是在一个节点上发生了什么
happens at one node so one a conditional distribution what happens so a node
分布发生了什么，因此给定节点X的节点条件分布是
distribution what happens so a node condition distribution given node X are
condition distribution given node X are given all my known condition on may all
鉴于我所有已知的条件，可能只有前面提到的，您的V
given all my known condition on may all only previous notes that V of you'll
only previous notes that V of you'll know that it's an exponential
知道这是一个指数族
know that it's an exponential exponential family is given by this
exponential family is given by this expression and I don't have a of beta
表达式，我没有beta，因为我放弃了比例
expression and I don't have a of beta because I have given up proportional
because I have given up proportional sign here where my sufficient statistics
在这里签名，我足够的统计信息就是这些变量和这些变量
sign here where my sufficient statistics is just our these variables and these
is just our these variables and these values and base parameter of these
值和这些值的基本参数还可以，因为我们
values and base parameter of these values okay the reason why because we
values okay the reason why because we are both we are doing node by node or
因为我们定义的是
are both we are doing node by node or basis because of that I defined that the
basis because of that I defined that the road condition institution okay next the
道路状况机构，接下来PMRF模型可以是民众贡献
road condition institution okay next the PMRF model can is the populace tribution
PMRF model can is the populace tribution which which can ranging from a
可以是均质的，也可以是混合的，然后是
which which can ranging from a homogeneous to or mixed one and then
homogeneous to or mixed one and then later from a node conditional
稍后从前面方程中的节点条件分布中，我们可以
later from a node conditional distribution in previous equation we can
distribution in previous equation we can that we can design up
我们可以通过节点距离来设计一个节点的PMR
that we can design up PMR for a node by node distance by
PMR for a node by node distance by choosing a decide of my base parameter
选择我的基本参数和我在VR中的正式身份的决定，然后查看
choosing a decide of my base parameter and my official status in the VR and see
and my official status in the VR and see oh yeah putting still BR and my based
哦，是的，继续放置BR和基于我的度量TR，请注意，这是一个联合
oh yeah putting still BR and my based measure TR and note that this is a joint
measure TR and note that this is a joint this is valid if I am able to obtain a
如果我能够获得θ的y值，但是我的Lθ是
this is valid if I am able to obtain a value for y of theta but my L theta is
value for y of theta but my L theta is computationally intractable so the
计算上难以处理，所以我们选择近似对数的原因
computationally intractable so the reason why we go for approximate log
reason why we go for approximate log likelihood okay so for example I don't
可能还好，例如，我不举一个通用的例子
likelihood okay so for example I don't give an example of a universal
give an example of a universal distribution where are my
将我的Sigma分配到哪里-如果我的
distribution where are my Sigma into the - and what happens if my
Sigma into the - and what happens if my lambda is in a structured graph so and
lambda在结构化图中，因此在此我们使用惩罚，因此
lambda is in a structured graph so and again in this we use a penalty so this
again in this we use a penalty so this one have taken it from the mouse we book
我们从书中摘录了第23章，我相信这是一本
one have taken it from the mouse we book chapter 23 I believe so this is an
chapter 23 I believe so this is an example so my lambda is very high so it
例子，所以我的lambda很高，所以它在本质上非常稀疏，为此我
example so my lambda is very high so it is very sparse in nature and for this my
is very sparse in nature and for this my lambda is equal to 0 so it is very dense
lambda等于0，所以它在本质上非常密集，因此我的lambda给了我一个非常
lambda is equal to 0 so it is very dense in nature so my lambda gives me a very
in nature so my lambda gives me a very big spectrum of my specificity okay so
我的特异性范围很大，所以下一个亲本是大概的
big spectrum of my specificity okay so next a parent thing is the approximate
next a parent thing is the approximate maximum like you know make you so we go
像你知道的那样使你最大化，所以我们去赢利，因为theta值很高
maximum like you know make you so we go for a profit because a of theta as high
for a profit because a of theta as high dimensional integral and it's typically
尺寸积分，它通常是棘手的，为了做到这一点，我们
dimensional integral and it's typically intractable and in order to do this we
intractable and in order to do this we replace your theta with intractable or
用难以解决的或凸出的theta值代替您的theta或为我
replace your theta with intractable or convex upper value of theta or for my
convex upper value of theta or for my problem for proceeding for me to obtain
让我着手获得theta的T Tauri的价值的问题，因此
problem for proceeding for me to obtain our value for U of T Tauri of theta so
our value for U of T Tauri of theta so we need we need to recall all
我们需要回忆起所有的耐心，因为从我的意思是
we need we need to recall all patience because from the I mean a
patience because from the I mean a different paper so in order to have a
不同的纸张，以便具有紧凑的符号
different paper so in order to have a compact notation
compact notation I just recall everything again so theta
我只是再次回忆起一切，所以theta是我的自然参数，成为您的
I just recall everything again so theta is my natural parameter and be your
is my natural parameter and be your purchase my sufficient statistics and
购买我足够的统计信息，它在此域中，也包括我的内部
purchase my sufficient statistics and it's in this domain and also my inner
it's in this domain and also my inner product is expressed in this fashion
产品以这种方式表达，我们都记得几张幻灯片
product is expressed in this fashion which we all remember few slides back
which we all remember few slides back and also here the new thing is we're
这也是我们要在其中定义均值参数的新事物
and also here the new thing is we're going to define the mean parameters in
going to define the mean parameters in this fashion and this is for my for my
这种时尚，这是我的优势，主要的是我的优势，我的优势
this fashion and this is for my for my edge so main one is for my edge and my
edge so main one is for my edge and my expectation of the VR of X is nothing
对X的VR的期望不过是我的mu R，对于
expectation of the VR of X is nothing but my mu R and for the similarly for
but my mu R and for the similarly for the S parameter and also one more
S参数，还有一个更重要的事情是您将
the S parameter and also one more important thing is you are going to
important thing is you are going to express it and the Google map the for
表示它，然后Google将该节点的X参数与X映射为
express it and the Google map the for the node and the X parameter with the in
the node and the X parameter with the in this matrix okay the reason I mentioned
这个矩阵好吧，我之所以提到它，是因为在本书和
this matrix okay the reason I mentioned it because in this book and the
it because in this book and the surrealist paper
超现实主义的纸乔丹纸，他为
surrealist paper Jordan paper he gives an expression for
Jordan paper he gives an expression for the upper bound the lock partition
theta的锁分区功能的上限如下
the upper bound the lock partition function of theta has the following
function of theta has the following upper bound and here the same notations
上限和相同的符号，此处使用的是不同的报告
upper bound and here the same notations what a different report is used here in
what a different report is used here in this paper and this is just a brief
这篇论文，这只是对他如何获得此的简要说明
this paper and this is just a brief explanation of how he has obtained this
explanation of how he has obtained this one so in particularly we obtain the
因此，特别是我们获得了
one so in particularly we obtain the upper bound relationship between the
upper bound relationship between the entropy H of X and the entropy of the
X的熵H和由此得到的结点势的熵
entropy H of X and the entropy of the node potential given by this in addition
node potential given by this in addition to the different choices of L R where R
到LR的不同选择，因为我在Pino中有R
to the different choices of L R where R because I have in my Pino does this
because I have in my Pino does this thing so it's goes from R 1 to P 4 or
所以它是从R 1到P 4或异构域，所以我有这个
thing so it's goes from R 1 to P 4 or heterogeneous domains so I have this
heterogeneous domains so I have this expression for a of theta now is by
现在表达the theta是通过奉献这个双重的你
expression for a of theta now is by taking the dedication of this dual you
taking the dedication of this dual you can convert this high dimension problem
可以根据上述定理转换这个高维问题，即
can convert this high dimension problem from the above theorem and that is
from the above theorem and that is orderable mention equation to the
可调用提及形式或可处理形式的有序提及方程，以便
orderable mention equation to the calling or tractable form so that the
calling or tractable form so that the same expression we can write in this
我们可以在其中写出相同的表达式，其中F表示为2
same expression we can write in this where F of 2 is expressed in the
where F of 2 is expressed in the equation here later we are going to plug
等式在这里，我们将插入theta到主
equation here later we are going to plug in this a of theta into the main
in this a of theta into the main equation here
等式在这里
进入这里的主要方程式，然后对其进行简化，我们得到
in this a of theta into the main equation here
into the main equation here and then later simplifying it we obtain this
进入这里的主要方程式，然后对其进行简化，我们得到
later simplifying it we obtain this optimization problem available to
优化问题可用于最小化此问题，这是我的问题
optimization problem available to minimize this and where this is my
minimize this and where this is my different matrix we have a theta belongs
我们有一个theta属于不同的矩阵，这个表达式什么都不是
different matrix we have a theta belongs to and this this expression is nothing
to and this this expression is nothing but the expression that we had observed
但是我们昨天在科迪·贝克（Cody Baker）解释时所观察到的表情
but the expression that we had observed when Cody Baker explained that yesterday
when Cody Baker explained that yesterday yesterday afternoon so when he explained
昨天下午，所以当他向这个小组解释图形时，昨天
yesterday afternoon so when he explained this group graphical so yesterday so
this group graphical so yesterday so this is something similar to that so to
这与之类似，因此要使其分组，所以我们要做的是
this is something similar to that so to make it group so what we do is we for a
make it group so what we do is we for a zero-mean graph a Gaussian amara with
零均值图具有附加约束的高斯阿玛拉
zero-mean graph a Gaussian amara with additional constraint that is
有条件地独立，那么我们要做的是研究为0，在这种情况下
conditionally independent then what we do is we study to 0 and in that case
do is we study to 0 and in that case profit is equal to the graphical Rezo
利润等于图形Rezo，但
profit is equal to the graphical Rezo but there's one difference in the
but there's one difference in the optimization procedure what he or what
优化过程他或他遵循的内容以及遵循的内容
optimization procedure what he or what he has followed and what is followed
he has followed and what is followed here in that the graphical ticket
这是因为图形凭单相对于
here in that the graphical ticket optimizes you with respect to the
optimizes you with respect to the empirical covariance matrix but in our
经验协方差矩阵，但是在我们的情况下或我们要做的是
empirical covariance matrix but in our case or what we do is we optimize with
case or what we do is we optimize with respect to using the sample average of
关于使用EMR的足够统计量的样本平均值
respect to using the sample average of the sufficient statistics of the EMRs
the sufficient statistics of the EMRs those things we are talking about the
我们正在谈论的有关优化过程的那些事情
those things we are talking about the optimization procedure we are going to
optimization procedure we are going to this alternating direction or method of
这个交替的方向或乘数的方法，我只是给你一个简短的
this alternating direction or method of multipliers and I just give you a brief
multipliers and I just give you a brief explanation of what DMMs and then and
解释什么数字万用表，然后再解释一下
explanation of what DMMs and then and then explain again like how the being
then explain again like how the being implemented so this is just a small
实现，所以这只是一个小小的解释和算法，
implemented so this is just a small explanation and algorithm which also
explanation and algorithm which also complex optimization problem by breaking
通过分解成较小的部分可以解决复杂的优化问题
complex optimization problem by breaking into smaller pieces each other which can
into smaller pieces each other which can easily then be handled example it is
容易然后被处理的示例，这被认为是客观的
easily then be handled example it is considered this would be objective
considered this would be objective function we have to minimize this
函数我们必须最小化X的目标函数f加上Z的G
function we have to minimize this objective function f of X plus G of Z
objective function f of X plus G of Z and we have to design variables
我们必须设计变量X和Z
and we have to design variables X and Z which is subjected to a
X and Z which is subjected to a constraint that is our 8 plus B Z equals
我们的8加BZ等于T的约束，现在我们定义一个参数a
constraint that is our 8 plus B Z equals T and now we define an argument a
T and now we define an argument a Lagrangian with the three parameter Rho
拉格朗日的三个参数Rho或刚好大于零，我们说
Lagrangian with the three parameter Rho or just greater than zero and we say
or just greater than zero and we say that is nothing but the objective
那不过是目标函数加上这个的uu转置而已
that is nothing but the objective function plus u u transpose of this
function plus u u transpose of this constraint here plus my LP parameter to
这里的约束加上我的LP参数到规范，我们为X更新了
constraint here plus my LP parameter to the norm and what we do we update X for
the norm and what we do we update X for updating X we take the value of Z of the
更新X时，我们将获取先前剪辑的Z值，而您将获取先前剪辑的Z值
updating X we take the value of Z of the previous clip and you of the previous
previous clip and you of the previous clip and then later or we update Z when
剪辑，然后稍后进行更新，或者当我们更新Z时我们更新Z我们取更新后的值
clip and then later or we update Z when we updating Z we take the updated value
we updating Z we take the updated value of x and then we update we update the D
的x，然后我们更新，我们更新了D，但我们没有开发更新
of x and then we update we update the D but we we do not have the update develop
but we we do not have the update develop view so we are using the previous
视图，所以我们在这里使用以前的更新值，然后我们得到
view so we are using the previous updated value here and later we get the
updated value here and later we get the closed form or solution with with with
在此处带有此表达式的封闭形式或解决方案，这就是原因
closed form or solution with with with this expression here and that is reason
this expression here and that is reason why it is known as alternating direction
为什么将其称为交变方向，因为我们为X做它，然后为
why it is known as alternating direction because we do it for X then we do it for
because we do it for X then we do it for Z and then we do it again at last for
Z，然后我们再次针对英国的封闭式解决方案再次进行操作，我是说，
Z and then we do it again at last for closed form solution for UK I mean so we
closed form solution for UK I mean so we do it until the stop criterion is
这样做直到提到停止标准为止，所以通常这样
do it until the stop criterion is mentioned so this is in general so
mentioned so this is in general so basically we have to update these three
基本上，我们必须更新这三个参数才能解决此问题
basically we have to update these three parameters coming back to this problem
parameters coming back to this problem here we dated again saying that we have
在这里，我们再次约会，说我们必须将其最小化，然后您再次说
here we dated again saying that we have to minimize this and again you say that
to minimize this and again you say that we have to update three things theta big
我们必须更新theta big的三件事，而您则是同一件事，但对于
we have to update three things theta big and you it is the same thing but for
and you it is the same thing but for this problem we prom late top-40 to
这个问题我们会向前40名舞会进行更新，这是eta的公式
this problem we prom late top-40 to update this is the formulation where eta
update this is the formulation where eta is nothing but Rho by n and this is
只是Rho乘n而已，而Q就是我的分解，
is nothing but Rho by n and this is nothing but Q this my decomposition and
nothing but Q this my decomposition and later for Z update again this is the
稍后再次进行Z更新，这是我们已经看到的表达式
later for Z update again this is the expression which we have already seen
expression which we have already seen and also this is from a you updated cell
而且这是从您更新的手机解决方案中获得的，因此我可以
and also this is from a you updated cell phone solution so I'll be able to get an
phone solution so I'll be able to get an optimum value okay I mean it is used for
最佳值好吧，我的意思是它用于可视化晶圆以检查
optimum value okay I mean it is used for to visualize the wafer to inspect the
to visualize the wafer to inspect the performance of classification and in
性能的分类，在此我们有两个x轴和y轴
performance of classification and in this we have two x axis and y axis which
this we have two x axis and y axis which is to positive and false positive and
是肯定的还是假的，我的读书俱乐部就在我角落的一部分
is to positive and false positive and my book club is part of my corner then
my book club is part of my corner then the system is accurate its operating the
该系统是准确的其操作场地，并且由于该区域下方
the system is accurate its operating the venue and since the area under this
venue and since the area under this curve gives me the appreciation okay I
曲线给了我欣赏，好吧，我做了一个小玩具问题，因为我做了
curve gives me the appreciation okay I took a small toy problem because I did
took a small toy problem because I did not get the data set what the paper has
无法获得本文执行的数据集，因此在此论坛中
not get the data set what the paper has implemented so in this in this forum
implemented so in this in this forum I've taken eight Bernoulli eight gamma
我取了八伯努利八伽马八高斯，做了蒸馏。
I've taken eight Bernoulli eight gamma eight Gaussian and made a distillate
eight Gaussian and made a distillate with K is equal to 3 and there are two
当K等于3时，有两种情况，一种具有权力，另一种是
with K is equal to 3 and there are two cases one has power he other is the
cases one has power he other is the dense case was fast case taken or the
密集案例是快速案例，或者存在的潜力的10％，并且
dense case was fast case taken or the 10% of the potential that exists and the
10% of the potential that exists and the for dense case have taken the 50% of the
对于稠密的情况，采取了50％的潜在边存在，然后这些是
for dense case have taken the 50% of the potential edge exists and then these are
potential edge exists and then these are the results that have obtained this is
得到的结果是关于高度结构化和这个世界的
the results that have obtained this is for highly structure and this world
for highly structure and this world knows fast structure and we can observe
知道快速的结构，我们可以观察到它们说明了
knows fast structure and we can observe that the the that they illustrate the de
that the the that they illustrate the de Graaff with the high degree of sparsity
格拉夫具有高度的稀疏性，可以回收很少的样品
Graaff with the high degree of sparsity to recover few samples it is much
to recover few samples it is much possible so that is this is much better
可能，这是更好的了，这只是说明，还可以
possible so that is this is much better that is the illustrate just and ok again
that is the illustrate just and ok again this is the same I'm going to conclude
这就是我要得出结论的结论，因此在这项工作中
this is the same I'm going to conclude to conclude this so in this work we have
to conclude this so in this work we have discussed the method for learning the
讨论了学习马尔可夫网络的方法
discussed the method for learning the Markov networks that is from
Markov networks that is from observational data and then this PMRF is
观测数据，然后这个PMRF是一个多元天才数据，
observational data and then this PMRF is a multivariate genius data which is much
a multivariate genius data which is much required for example you take our
例如您需要我们的医疗数据库或类似的数据库
required for example you take our medical database or something like that
medical database or something like that and then we have not used the exact use
然后我们没有为此使用确切的使用近似最大似然
and then we have not used the exact use approximate maximum likelihood for this
approximate maximum likelihood for this problem and you also developed our a DMM
问题，您还开发了一种DMM算法，可以减少我
problem and you also developed our a DMM algorithm which can reduce me a
algorithm which can reduce me a closed-form updates and these are the
封闭形式的更新，这些是参考，摘自本文或
closed-form updates and these are the references and from this paper or taken
references and from this paper or taken the like the main people that have
像那些努力并进一步获得theta的主要人物
the like the main people that have effort and further to obtain a of theta
effort and further to obtain a of theta I hope that theta the upper bound refers
我希望theta上限是本文的参考，并且本文给出了一个
I hope that theta the upper bound refers for this paper and this paper gives a
for this paper and this paper gives a brief explanation of early how do we go
早期的简要说明我们如何使用约
brief explanation of early how do we go about of using the approximately
哦
Oh
所以您好，我希望物理系能够
so hi I am a wishing that from the physics department the generation of the
physics department the generation of the handwritten like image using variational
使用可变自动编码器手写的图像，它已经在
handwritten like image using variational auto encoder it has been trained on the
auto encoder it has been trained on the eminence to dataset the outline is that
突出数据集的轮廓是关于介绍的一些内容
eminence to dataset the outline is that introduction a little bit about
introduction a little bit about missionaries which are like standard we
像标准的传教士，我们从扫描仪自动编码器开始
missionaries which are like standard we start with scanner auto encoder we
start with scanner auto encoder we introduced variation on experience
介绍了经验变化的外部颜色变化-
introduced variation on experience variational outside color -
variational outside color - normalization and the resultant clock so
归一化和结果时钟，所以我将在
normalization and the resultant clock so I'll be talking about a little bit in
I'll be talking about a little bit in little about this machineries because I
关于这台机器的知识很少，因为我在开始之后就了解了它们
little about this machineries because I learned about them while starting after
learned about them while starting after starting working on this project itself
开始从事这个项目本身
因此，自动编码器网络是一对真正相连的网络
learned about them while starting after starting working on this project itself
so an autoencoder network is a pair of true connected networks
编码器组件制作并获取原始数据的表示形式
the encoder component makes and gains the representation of the original data
the representation of the original data Angele la or grid of pixels and then we
Angele la或像素网格，然后我们将n个颜色信息和
Angele la or grid of pixels and then we call that n color information and the
call that n color information and the decoder part decodes it back to the
解码器部分将其解码回原始尺寸，通常高于
decoder part decodes it back to the original dimension usually higher than
original dimension usually higher than the dimensional representation like this
像这样的尺寸表示就是描述
the dimensional representation like this this is the description
所以通常解码器网络的输出与输入不匹配
so in general the output of the decoder network would not match with the input
network would not match with the input using the input data point like new data
使用输入数据点（如新数据点），它会告诉您，因为它不会
using the input data point like new data points then it tells because it won't
points then it tells because it won't it can only give must output replicating
它只能给必须输出复制我们更密集的表示
it can only give must output replicating the denser representation of our
the denser representation of our original input so it cannot create new
原始输入，因此它无法创建新事物，因此就是这样
original input so it cannot create new things so it's that's that's where
things so it's that's that's where standard auto encoder slack so these are
标准自动编码器松弛，因此这些只是表示形式的示例
standard auto encoder slack so these are kind of an example of the representation
kind of an example of the representation of the MST data state where we have like
MST数据状态的状态，我们有28到28
of the MST data state where we have like twenty eighteen to twenty eighth
twenty eighteen to twenty eighth dimension we have converted it to the
维度，我们已将其转换为二维，因此它们的分布和
dimension we have converted it to the two dimension so their distribution and
two dimension so their distribution and it's kind of get rich there is no
这是一种致富，代表不存在连续性
it's kind of get rich there is no continuity from one the representation
continuity from one the representation data point of one visit to the other so
一次访问另一个访问的数据点，因此我们不希望这样，因为它在哪里
data point of one visit to the other so we won't want that because where it's
we won't want that because where it's difficult to general
很难像分布那样的一般模型
difficult to general models while the distribution is like
models while the distribution is like that in generative models we would not
在生成模型中，我们不想复制使用它的数据
that in generative models we would not want to replicate data that we used it
want to replicate data that we used it to train in the first place but also we
首先训练，但我们也想从
to train in the first place but also we want to sample data points from the
want to sample data points from the distribution the latent space and decode
分配潜在空间并对其进行解码，以形成大臣官邸和更高的
distribution the latent space and decode them to form Chancellor's and the higher
them to form Chancellor's and the higher data points so suppose we we have a lot
数据点，所以假设我们有很多手写数字的数据点
data points so suppose we we have a lot of data points of the handwritten digits
of data points of the handwritten digits and we want to create a model to get the
我们想要创建一个模型来获得生命周期的概率分布
and we want to create a model to get the probability distribution of life of
probability distribution of life of those data points now these images are
这些数据点现在这些图像按趋势年龄为28，以便获得最大
those data points now these images are 28 by trend age so to get a maximum
28 by trend age so to get a maximum likelihood would have to get a min of 28
可能性必须是将28的最小值变成28的维，并且协方差
likelihood would have to get a min of 28 into 28 dimension and and the covariance
into 28 dimension and and the covariance matrix of the similar dimensions those
尺寸相似的矩阵，它们在计算上非常难处理
matrix of the similar dimensions those are very computationally intractable
are very computationally intractable that's why the idea of auto-encoders
这就是为什么自动编码器的想法首先应运而生的原因
that's why the idea of auto-encoders comes into play in the first place to
comes into play in the first place to get a more compressed representation so
从概率图形模型中获得更压缩的表示
get a more compressed representation so from the probabilistic graphical models
from the probabilistic graphical models from what we can say
从我们可以说的
[音乐]
from the probabilistic graphical models from what we can say
[Music]
分母本身很难计算非常昂贵
in the denominator itself is very difficult to compute very expensive
difficult to compute very expensive that's why we use variation insurance to
这就是为什么我们使用差异保险来估算与一个家庭的后验
that's why we use variation insurance to approximate the posterior with a family
approximate the posterior with a family of distribution which represents the
分布代表我们的分布参数
of distribution which represents the parameters of the distributions we are
parameters of the distributions we are trying to fit for example a cube or a
试图适合例如多维数据集或正态分布，这将意味着新的
trying to fit for example a cube or a normal distribution it will mean the new
normal distribution it will mean the new X I and Sigma X we will use KL
XI和Sigma X我们将使用KL散度来量化
X I and Sigma X we will use KL divergence which should quantify the
divergence which should quantify the information lost we try to replace the
信息丢失，我们尝试用lambda替换主分布P
information lost we try to replace the primary distribution P with lambda
因为是的，杀死差异被定义为预期的期望值
for that yeah kill divergences define as the expected expectation value of the
the expected expectation value of the log of Q lambda over P and we can
P上的Q lambda的对数，我们可以在那里表示减法群
log of Q lambda over P and we can express in there the subtractive swarm
express in there the subtractive swarm and using Bayes theorem we can express
并使用贝叶斯定理，我们可以将其表示为方程二
and using Bayes theorem we can express it in the like a form of equation two
像这里，最佳姿势的近似值很清楚，我发誓要得到
like here the approximate for optimal posture is clear I swore to get
posture is clear I swore to get approximate optimal posture we minimize
近似最佳姿势，我们将lambda的KL散度减至最小
approximate optimal posture we minimize KL divergence with respect to lambda to
KL divergence with respect to lambda to get the optimized Q lambda but the
得到优化的Q lambda，但是直到丢失为止，px的难解的对数
get the optimized Q lambda but the intractable term log of px till lost
intractable term log of px till lost within the expression of the KL
在这样的KL散度的表达中等于
within the expression of the KL divergence like this is equal to that
divergence like this is equal to that and that term is very computationally
该术语在计算上非常昂贵，因此我们要删除该术语
and that term is very computationally expensive so we want to remove that
expensive so we want to remove that that's why we just flip side and Express
这就是为什么我们只是反过来表示为这种减法形式
that's why we just flip side and Express as this subtractive form of to
as this subtractive form of to expectation values plus KL divergence
期望值加上KL散度现在我们知道KL散度总是
expectation values plus KL divergence now we know that KL divergence is always
now we know that KL divergence is always non-negative so it's I'm sorry so its
非负数，所以很抱歉，其最小值为0，以便将其最大化
non-negative so it's I'm sorry so its minimum value is 0 so to maximize this
minimum value is 0 so to maximize this we want to minimize this and maximum
我们要最小化此排放并最大程度地排放，所以现在这有点
we want to minimize this and maximum discharge so now this becomes a bit
discharge so now this becomes a bit tractable to compute
易于计算
和信息保险，我们使用工会投票将Forrester放入Thomas
discharge so now this becomes a bit tractable to compute
and informational insurance we use union vo checking Forrester into the Thomas
和信息保险，我们使用工会投票将Forrester放入Thomas
vo checking Forrester into the Thomas Trump's dependent only upon the single
特朗普仅依赖于单个数据点，因此可以使用
Trump's dependent only upon the single data points this allows for the use of
data points this allows for the use of stochastic gradient descent with respect
关于参数λ变化的随机梯度下降
stochastic gradient descent with respect to the variation of parameters lambda
to the variation of parameters lambda for a given data point X right the LPO
对于给定的数据点X右，LPO在此定义，因此T超过
for a given data point X right the LPO are defined on this so long T exceeds
给定Z减去Q lambda Disney的P的对数期望
expectation of log of P of a given Z minus Q lambda Disney different extend
minus Q lambda Disney different extend teasing minus KL divergence of Q lambda
在给定X的情况下取QλZ的减负KL散度，在给定X的情况下取笑，因此我们想
teasing minus KL divergence of Q lambda Z given X and P Z given X so we want to
Z given X and P Z given X so we want to optimize log tapes by trying to find a
通过尝试找到内部的数量下限来优化日志磁带
optimize log tapes by trying to find a lower bound of the quantity inside the
lower bound of the quantity inside the curly bracket computationally
大括号在计算上难以处理，这是一个最大的示例
curly bracket computationally intractable maximizing this is a sample
intractable maximizing this is a sample PC is really in the latent space also we
PC确实处于潜在空间，我们还可以增加获得封闭空间的优势
PC is really in the latent space also we can add an advantage of obtaining closed
can add an advantage of obtaining closed formulation of the KL divergence which
KL散度的公式，在给定X的情况下，将看到Z和Q lambda Z
formulation of the KL divergence which will see Z and Q lambda Z given X we
will see Z and Q lambda Z given X we check easy to the standard normal
容易检查均值0和标准的标准正态分布
check easy to the standard normal distribution with mean 0 and standard
distribution with mean 0 and standard deviation is 1 and 2 lambda Z given X to
给定X为1时，偏差为1和2λZ
deviation is 1 and 2 lambda Z given X to be
be like this also another normal
这样也是另一个正态分布，这就是协方差
like this also another normal distribution here this is the covariance
distribution here this is the covariance matrices constraint to the diagonal
对角矩阵的矩阵约束以使计算容易，但是
matrices constraint to the diagonal matrix to keep computation easy but
matrix to keep computation easy but final the final expression is easy if
如果我们得到封闭形式的表达式，则最终表达式很容易
final the final expression is easy if the closed form expression that we get
the closed form expression that we get by some algebraic manipulation is the
通过代数运算得到的归一化非常有用
by some algebraic manipulation is the normalization which is a very useful
normalization which is a very useful technique introduced to improve the
引入技术以改善GAE和一般视野的性能
technique introduced to improve the performance of GAE and in general vision
f3隐藏层的归一化输出在每个mini上标准化
normalization output of f3 hidden layer is standardized over every single mini
is standardized over every single mini batch path in the training session it
在培训课程中的批处理路径很明显，假设我们有一个
batch path in the training session it will be clear suppose we have a
will be clear suppose we have a classifier and we want the classifier to
分类器，我们希望分类器在一些图像之间进行分类
classifier and we want the classifier to classify between some images which
classify between some images which contents cat and which doesn't have a
内容为猫，并且图像中没有猫，因此我们的训练数据
contents cat and which doesn't have a cat in the image so our training data
cat in the image so our training data contents on the black cat and all other
黑猫和所有其他非猫图像上的内容，然后将
contents on the black cat and all other non cat images and then will be after
non cat images and then will be after training we introduced cat images which
训练中，我们介绍了一般来说是彩色猫和非猫的猫图像
training we introduced cat images which are colorful cat in general and non cat
are colorful cat in general and non cat or transfer won't be trouble too far
或转移不会像它所做的那么麻烦那么遥远
or transfer won't be trouble too far from that good as it did for the
from that good as it did for the training dataset this is called this is
训练数据集，这被称为这是一个非常奇特的术语，称为协变量平移
training dataset this is called this is a very fancy term called covariate shift
a very fancy term called covariate shift which means the a shift in the data
这意味着数据点在其分布中发生了偏移
which means the a shift in the data point in its distribution
情境模型
situation model
因此，假设黑猫的数据部分-像这样的数据
so suppose the the data parts of black cats - like this very thing the data
cats - like this very thing the data points and the non cats are like this
点和非猫就像这个黑色的十字架，所以通常每个可怜的人
points and the non cats are like this black crosses so usually this poor each
black crosses so usually this poor each we don't use vaginal normalization our
我们不使用阴道标准化，我们的模型可能会学习直线
we don't use vaginal normalization our model would likely learn straight line
model would likely learn straight line difference we should separate these data
区别，当我们
difference we should separate these data points like this straight line when we
points like this straight line when we introduced these colorful cats these
介绍了这些五颜六色的猫这些五颜六色的猫线的这些数据点
introduced these colorful cats these data points of this colorful cat lines
data points of this colorful cat lines here which our model won't be able to
在这里我们的模型将无法正确分类，因为现在他们
here which our model won't be able to classify it correctly because now they
classify it correctly because now they have only joined a straight line which
仅加入了一条直线，显然无法对其进行准确分类
have only joined a straight line which clearly don't classify them accurately
clearly don't classify them accurately that so that's why we want to we want to
这就是为什么我们想要使用批处理规范化的原因，即使
that so that's why we want to we want to use batch normalization so that even if
use batch normalization so that even if our data points to vary by some amount
如果将其归一化，我们的数据点将有所变化，并且我们的模型
our data points to vary by some amount if normalizes it back and our our model
if normalizes it back and our our model learns faster learns more reliable
学习更快，学习更可靠，更密集
learns faster learns more reliable denser representation
这些是使用标准化的优势，这使我们
these are some advantages of using that's normalization which makes our
that's normalization which makes our model to launch faster makes it converge
更快发布的模型使其能够以更高的价值和更快的速度更好地融合
model to launch faster makes it converge better in a better value and in a faster
better in a better value and in a faster manner while each training iteration
方式，而每次训练迭代都会变得有些偏斜，因为
manner while each training iteration will become somewhat skewer because the
will become somewhat skewer because the externalization calculations in the
正向路径中的外部化计算，但最终它将
externalization calculations in the forward path but eventually it would
forward path but eventually it would converge quickly to overall combination
迅速融合到整体组合中，因为口袋是我用来
converge quickly to overall combination because pockets these are the I used for
because pockets these are the I used for layer deep fully connected Network as
层深层全连接网络既是编码器又是解码器萨尔萨舞
layer deep fully connected Network as both encoder and decoder salsa eminence
both encoder and decoder salsa eminence together set I take one more minute this
一起设置我需要一分钟，这是
together set I take one more minute this is the
是的，所以这是失去功能的收敛而没有使用合理化
yeah so this is the convergence of lost function without using rationalization
function without using rationalization and this is the generated data set
这是没有合理化的生成的数据集，接下来我被使用
and this is the generated data set without rationalization next I am used
without rationalization next I am used batch normalization and the it converges
批归一化，它收敛到更好的值，这是一个更好的值
batch normalization and the it converges to a better value which is a bit more
to a better value which is a bit more cleaner
清洁工
这些使用的是拉丁扭曲的四个四个维度，而不是两个
to a better value which is a bit more cleaner
these are using the four four dimensions for the Latin twist instead of two with
这些使用的是拉丁扭曲的四个四个维度，而不是两个
for the Latin twist instead of two with without BN this is again it using BM so
如果没有BN，这也是使用BM的原因，因此您可以看到损失函数
without BN this is again it using BM so you can see that the loss function
访客参考
visitor references
[掌声]
[Applause]